quadrigacx.com 2018-08-14

# Quadriga Coin Exchange | Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Policy outlines the manner in which QuadrigaCX collects, maintains, uses, stores, and discloses information collected from users of the QuadrigaCX website and any related service provided by QuadrigaCX and its associates. This policy applies to all products and services offered by QuadrigaCX.

Throughout this policy, QuadrigaCX is referred to as "us", "our", "we", "the website", and "Quadriga". Users of QuadrigaCX include but are not limited to registered members, as well as any visitor who uses the website in any way, shape or form. The privacy policy also applies to any automated system accessing any part of the QuadrigaCX Platform, whether it be through our API or any other means. This privacy policy also applies to any form of communication with QuadrigaCX, its employees, directors, and associates, including but not limited to email or telephone communications.

## Gathering Personal Information

In order to comply with KYC and anti-money laundering regulations, QuadrigaCX may request certain information from registered users, including your name, date of birth, address, photo identification, email address, phone number, or any other personally identifiable information. Furthermore, QuadrigaCX may request such information to prevent fraud, and to protect QuadrigaCX in any way that we deem reasonable.

## Storage of Personal Information

All sensitive and private data collected by QuadrigaCX is stored in an encrypted format. To achieve the highest levels of security and privacy, communication between your computer/device is secured using SSL.

## Use of Personal Information

QuadrigaCX may collect and use personal information for the following purposes:

  * To protect our system from fraud
  * To provide and improve customer service
  * To comply with KYC regulations
  * To send period emails
  * To contact users using any means that we deem necessary
  * To process payments, including fundings and withdrawals
  * To comply with any provincial or national law
  * To carry out the regular business activities of QuadrigaCX

QuadrigaCX will not disclose your personal information to any third party. However, as we deem reasonable, your information may be shared with any division of QuadrigaCX or its subsidiaries in order to provide the best possible user experience. We will not sell, trade or rent any personal information provided to QuadrigaCX with any third party. We will not share your information with any government agency, unless required to do so by law.

## European General Data Protection Regulation

The following portions of our privacy policy apply specifically to European users and are designed to comply with GDPR regulations.

### Information Specifics

QuadrigaCX specifically gathers the following information from users:

  * IP addresses
  * Browser information
  * User agent information
  * Cookie information (Persistent and Session Cookies)

Users who create accounts are asked to provide:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Phone Number
  * Date of birth
  * Email Address
  * ID documentation for KYC/AML procedures

Additional Information that may be requested:

  * Banking information
  * Additional KYC information
  * Cryptocurrency address information

### Legal Basis for data collection

If you are from the European Economic Area, our legal basis for collecting and using personal information described above depends on the type of information collected and the context in which we collect it.

Information is collected to prevent fraud, comply with Canadian legislation and to prevent money laundering. Furthermore, information is collected to facilitate the services that we provide (For example, banking information to send payments to your account.)

Information that is collected from our users is stored in compliance with Canadian privacy legislation and AML/KYC legislation. In compliance with European regulations, European users may request a copy of all information that we store pertaining to their account at any time.

All European user data is stored in an encrypted format on European servers. The information may be access by employees of QuadrigaCX located in Europe or Canada in order to provide services to our European users. When this occurs, information is transmitted in an encrypted format to ensure the highest level of data protection.

All users may request that their account be closed at any time from within the account settings section of their account. Additionally, European users may request that their information be permanently deleted from our systems.

By using QuadrigaCX, you accept the above privacy policy. If you do not accept this policy, please leave QuadrigaCX immediately. Continued use of QuadrigaCX or any of our services constitutes your acceptance of these terms. QuadrigaCX may modify this policy at any time. Please review this policy regularly.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at contact@quadrigacx.com
